Guide to the Joe David Bellamy Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- June 2000 Acquisition, 1967-2000; 1; 44.13; (55 boxes)
  - Writing, Editorial, and Project Files
    - Order forms for Suzi Sinzinnati, the Frozen Sea, undated (Box 44)
    - Final proof of [ Suzi Sinzinnati ], 1988 December 16; 3 (Box 44)
    - Spiral-bound proofs of Suzi Sinzinnati, 1989; 3 (Box 44)
    - Proof of Literary Luxuries, 1995 July 26; 2 (Box 44)
    - Literary Luxuries cover slicks, order forms, publicity, 1995 (Box 44)
    - Reprint permission notices, index notes, 1974-1995 (Box 44)
    - Typescript proof of Literary Luxuries, 1995; 4 (Box 44)
    - Essay on the Saranac Lake writers' conference, undated (Box 44)
    - Typescripts from [ Literary Luxuries ], undated (Box 44)
    - Music copyright information, permission notices for Suzi Sinzinnati, 1988; 3 (Box 44)
    - The North American Review (includes excerpt from Suzi Sinzinnati, 1980 September (Box 44)
    - Corrected proofs of Suzi Sinzinnati, with separate sheet of song credits, 1988 October 31; 2 (Box 45)
    - Spiral bound proofs of Suzi Sinzinnati, 1989; 3 (Box 45)
    - Bound typescript of Going Steady (early draft of Suzi Sinzinnati ), undated (Box 45)
    - Jerry Klinkowitz correspondence, 1972-1981; 7 (Box 45)
    - Mass mailings, 1988-1990 (Box 45)
    - Old Dominion University panel, undated (Box 45)
    - ODU Literary Festival (Box 45)
    - Melissa Bank, 1988, December 15, undated (Box 45)
    - Hilda Gregory letters to Joe David Bellamy, 1973-1976 (Box 45)
    - Elizabeth Inness-Brown letters to Joe David Bellamy, typescripts, 1976-2000; 2 (Box 45)
    - Elizabeth Inness-Brown letters to Joe David Bellamy, typescripts (coontinued), 1976-2000; 4 (Box 46)
    - G. E. Murray letters to Joe David Bellamy, 1973-1988; 5 (Box 46)
    - Ann Matos letters to Joe David Bellamy, 1974-1979 (Box 46)
    - Susan Quist letters to Joe David Bellamy, 1973-1974 (Box 46)
    - Christopher Zenowich letters to Joe David Bellamy, ms. (Box 46)
    - Miscellaneous letters, 1973-2000; 4 (Box 46)
    - Poetry copyright assignments, 1978 (Box 46)
    - Page proofs and correspondence regarding Olympic Gold Medalist and Ancestors, 1978 (Box 46)
    - Markbarry typescript samples, undated (Box 46)
    - Trim Roman Bold and Universe typescript samples, undated (Box 46)
    - Various typescript samples, undated (Box 46)
    - Cover and advertisement proofs for Olympic Gold Medalist, 1978 (Box 46)
    - Proofs for Ancestors, undated (Box 46)
    - Cover proofs for Olympic Gold Medalist, 1978 (Box 46)
    - Fiction International, Vols 2-12, 1974-1980; (7 microfilms) (Box 47)
    - Audiocassettes, interviews with writers, 1976-1992, undated; 30 (Box 48)
      Restricted fragile material. Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - Atwood / Brown / Dillard, Saranac, 1978; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246877)
      - Banks, R., Eng. 310, November 7; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246786)
      - Banks, R. Eng. 241, 1983 November 8; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246919)
      - Barth, undated; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246802)
      - Barth reading, undated; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246968)
      - Beattie, Ann at Saranac, 1977; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246869)
      - Crews, Harry, undated; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246984)
      - Crews, Harry, undated; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091247016)
      - Crews, Harry class, undated; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091247032)
      - Doctorow, Saranac, 1979; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246810)
      - Fellows, 1991 July 25; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246950)
      - Gardner, John reading, undated; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246992)
      - Godwin, Gail at Saranac, 1977; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246836)
      - Godwin / Hawkes at Saranac, 1976; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091247024)
      - Magazine editing panel, Saranac, 1977; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246851)
      - NEA Talk to Fellows, 1992 June 16; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246794)
      - NEA Fellows (1 of 2 audiocassettes), 1992; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246893)
        Starts partway into the tape.
      - NEA Fellows (2 of 2 audiocassettes), 1992; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246901)
      - Oates, J. C. at Saranac, 1977; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246844)
      - Simmons on Book Reviewing / Annual Fiction Panel, Saranac, 1979; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246885)
      - Sontag, Susan (1 of 3 audiocassettes), undated; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246745)
      - Sontag, Susan (2 of 3 audiocassettes), undated; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246752)
      - Sontag, Susan / Wolfe, Tom to airport (3 of 3 audiocassettes), undated; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246778)
      - Talk to Fellows, NEA, 1991 March 5; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246935)
      - Talk to Fellows, 1991 October 21; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246943)
      - Wolfe, Tom. WSLU, Houston, undated; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246760)
      - Writers' Conference Program #1, undated; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246828)
      - Wolfe, Tom, undated; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246976)
      - Wolfe, Tom, lecture and conversation, undated; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091246927)
      - Writers' Conference, WSLU, undated; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002091247008)
    - Ten Joe David Bellamy event name tags, undated (Box 49)
    - Mamuscript notes removed from books, undated (Box 49)
  - Oversize
    - Typescript proofs for John Domini's Bedlam, some incomplete, 1981; 26 (Box 50 (Oversize))
    - Typescript proofs for Elizabeth Inness-Brown's Satin Palms, some incomplete, 1981; 9 (Box 50 (Oversize))
    - Typescript proofs for Catherine Petroski's Gravity and Other Stories, some incomplete, 1981; 17 (Box 51 (Oversize))
    - Cover proofs for New Writers of the 80s (Box 51 (Oversize))
    - Typescript sample sheet, contents page for Fiction International 12, undated (Box 51 (Oversize))
    - Typescript sample sheets, undated; 2 (Box 51 (Oversize))
    - Proofs for Fiction International Vol. 1, 1973 Fall (Box 51 (Oversize))
    - Various proofs, covers, etc., 1979-1981 (Box 51 (Oversize))
    - Proofs for Fiction International 12, 1980; 3 (Box 52 (Oversize))
    - Cover proofs/drawings for Fiction International 14, 1982 (Box 52 (Oversize))
    - Olympic Gold Medalist: proofs, 1978 (Box 52 (Oversize))
    - American Poetry Observed: galley, 1984 (Box 53 (Oversize))
    - American Poetry Observed: galley proofs, undated (Box 53 (Oversize))
    - Poetry Now: magazine, 1976 (Box 53 (Oversize))
    - COSMEP Catalog, 1973 (Box 53 (Oversize))
    - Fiction International logo art, 1973 (Box 53 (Oversize))
    - Illustrations and proofs, 1973 January 12 (Box 54 (Oversize))
    - New York Times Book Review (4 issues, 7 duplicates), 1976-1977 (Box 54 (Oversize))
    - New York Times Book Review with review of Wolfe's Purple Decades, 1982 October 10 (Box 54 (Oversize))
    - Galley proof of introduction to Wolfe's The Purple Decades, 1982 (Box 55 (Oversize))
    - The Purple Decades: galley proofs, 1982 (Box 55 (Oversize))
    - Letter to Joe David Bellamy from Tom Wolfe, 1972 November 20 (Box 55 (Oversize))
- June 2000 Acquisition, circa 1976; 2; 0.88; (3 boxes)
  This portion of the collection contains Fiction International, writings, production files and proofs.
  Formerly classed as: Uncat MSS 892
  - Fiction International, circa 1976; 7 (Box 56)
  - Fiction International (continued), circa 1976; 2 (Box 57)
  - Fiction International (continued), undated; 2 (Box 58 (Oversize))
- October 2007 Acquisition, 1962-2007; 3; 16.67; (19 boxes, including 1 computer disk)
  Organized into eight subgroupings: Correspondence, New Fiction Files, Fiction International Files, Writing Files, Writings by Others, Professional Papers, Other Papers, and Audiocassettes.
  This portion of the collection includes correspondence, writings, research files, printed material and other papers.
  Boxe 76 (audiocassettes): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Box 77 (computer disk): Restricted Fragile Material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Formerly classed as: Uncat MSS 987
  - Correspondence
    - Abbott, Lee K., 1981 (Box 59)
    - Abish, Walter, 1975-1976 (Box 59)
    - Alberts, Laurie, 1988-2000 (Box 59)
    - Amick, Steve, 1988-2007 (Box 59)
    - (Anton) Dooley, Beth, 1975-1979 (Box 59)
    - Apple, Max, 1977 (Box 59)
    - Atwood, Margaret, 1978 (Box 59)
    - Barber, Asa, 1971-1989 (Box 59)
    - Barthelme, Donald, 1971-1978 (Box 59)
    - Baldwin, Neil, 1978 (Box 59)
    - Beattie, Ann, 2006 (Box 59)
    - Bender, Eleanor, 1978-1980 (Box 59)
    - Benedict, Dianne, 1979 (Box 59)
    - Bent, Ted, 1970-1976 (Box 59)
    - Bergé, Carol, 1974-1978 (Box 59)
    - Blaise, Clark, 1993-2006 (Box 59)
    - Blue, Adrienne, 1973-1976 (Box 59)
    - Brown, Rosellen, 1978-2006 (Box 59)
    - Bruchac, Joseph, 1973-1980 (Box 59)
    - Bumpus, Jeremy, 1980 (Box 59)
    - Burgin, Richard, circa 1986 (Box 59)
    - Burack, Sylvia, 1990-1993 (Box 59)
    - Canin, Ethan, 2003 (Box 59)
    - Carter, Howard, 1975-1977 (Box 59)
    - Casey, John, 1971-1973 (Box 59)
    - Cherry, Kelly, 1995-2006 (Box 59)
    - Cheuse, Alan, 1993 (Box 59)
    - Costa, Richard, 1972-1988 (Box 59)
    - Cox, Elizabeth, 2006 (Box 59)
    - Davison, Peter, 1968-1973 (Box 59)
    - Devine, Roger, 1990-1992 (Box 59)
    - Dillard, Annie, 1978-2006; 1 (Box 59)
      Related Materials
      There is an audiocassette related to this material. It includes a recording of two phone calls from Annie Dillard to Bellamy, as well as one phone call from Gail Godwin to Bellamy. It can be found in Box 76.
    - Phone calls from Annie Dillard, Gail Godwin, 2006; 1 (Box 76, Item barcode 39002091246737)
      Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult access services for further information.
      This audiocassette is related to a folder of material titled "Annie Dillard" in Box 59, reference number 996.
    - Doctorow, E.L., 1979-2006 (Box 59)
    - (Dodd) Hancock, Ellen, 1978-1979 (Box 59)
    - Domini, John, 1977-1989 (Box 59)
    - Drake, Albert, 1970-1978 (Box 59)
    - Eldredge, Larry, 1972 (Box 59)
    - Ensworth, Patricia, 1972-1975 (Box 59)
    - Fay, Julie, 1995 (Box 59)
    - Feirstein, Frederick, 1974-1989 (Box 59)
    - Regarding: Fiedler, Leslie (Box 59)
    - Fox, Robert, 1978-1993 (Box 59)
    - Fox, Siv Cedering, 1981 (Box 59)
    - Regarding: Gass, William (Box 59)
    - Gerber, Merrill Joan, 1996 (Box 59)
    - Gioseffi, Daniela, 1974-1983 (Box 59)
    - Godwin, Gail, 1977-1996 (Box 59)
    - Goldbarth, Albert, 1992-2007 (Box 59)
      Includes a second printing of Four Color Comics #223 April 1949, Walt Disney's Donald Duck in Lost in the Andes!, which has been signed and dedicated to Bellamy by Albert Goldbarth.
    - Gordon, Jaimy, 1991 (Box 60)
    - Hack, Richard and Robin McKean, 1972-1973 (Box 60)
    - Halpern, Daniel, 1979 (Box 60)
    - Harrison, Colin and Katheryn, 1989-2006 (Box 60)
    - Hawkes, John, 1971-1973 (Box 60)
    - Heath, Susan, 1976-1978 (Box 60)
    - Henderson, Bill, 1978-2003 (Box 60)
    - DeWitt, Henry, 1973-1989; 2 (Box 60)
    - Heyen, William, 1979 (Box 60)
    - Hunter, Mark, 1973-1974 (Box 60)
    - Inness-Brown, Elizabeth, 1980-2006 (Box 60)
    - Jen, Gish, 1983 (Box 60)
    - Kaplan, Bernie, 1966-1971 (Box 60)
    - Kisor, Henry, 1975-1989 (Box 60)
    - Kittredge, William, 1979 (Box 60)
    - Klappert, Peter, 1987-1988 (Box 60)
    - Klinkowitz, Jerome, 1971-1973 (Box 60)
    - Lathbury, Roger, 1988-2003 (Box 60)
    - Laggett, John, 1985-1986 (Box 60)
    - Lehmann-Haupt, Christopher, 1974 (Box 60)
    - Lindner, Robert, 1966-1967 (Box 60)
    - Lish, Gordon, 1993-1996 (Box 60)
    - Locke, Richard, 1972-1974 (Box 60)
    - Lurie, Alison, 1974 (Box 60)
    - Macauley, Robie and Pam Painter, 1978-1981 (Box 60)
    - Mccaffery, Larry, 1978 (Box 60)
    - McGraw, Peter and Milena, with Peter's Mother, 1967-1969 (Box 60)
    - McPherson, James Alan, 2002-2005 (Box 60)
    - Madden, David, 1977-2003 (Box 60)
    - Mason, Bobbie Ann, 1979-2006 (Box 60)
    - Murray, G.E., 1979 (Box 60)
    - Myers, Jack, 1988 (Box 60)
    - Norris, Joan, 1975 (Box 60)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol, 1977-1978 (Box 60)
    - Parks, Kitty, 1968-2007 (Box 60)
      Includes material relating to the Parks family, who had inspired characters within Bellamy's novel, Suzi Sinzinnati.
    - Perkins, Jim, 1975-1980 (Box 60)
    - Peterson, Mary, 1976-1977 (Box 60)
    - Petroski, Catherine, 1981-1988 (Box 60)
    - Phillips, Jayne Anne, 1978-2006 (Box 60)
    - Plummer, William, 1976-1979 (Box 60)
    - Poulin, Al, Jr., 1972-1980 (Box 60)
    - Price, Reynolds, 2004-2006 (Box 60)
    - Reiley, Coe, 1979-1980 (Box 60)
    - Robinson, Sally, 1977 (Box 60)
    - Rosenblatt, Roger, 1976 (Box 60)
    - Rudin, Louis D., Jr., 1964 (Box 61)
    - See, Carolyn, circa 1997-2007 (Box 61)
    - Serling, Rod, 1963-1978 (Box 61)
    - Simmons, Charles, 1979 (Box 61)
    - Snyder, Bob, 1975 (Box 61)
    - Sobin, Anthony, 1976-1977 (Box 61)
    - Solotaroff, Ted, 1971-1975 (Box 61)
    - Spires, Elizabeth, 1979-1985 (Box 61)
    - Stagg, David, III., 1966-1982 (Box 61)
    - Stevick, Philip, 1975 (Box 61)
    - Strieber, Whitley, 2006 (Box 61)
    - Sukenick, Lynn, 1971-1972 (Box 61)
    - Sukenick, Ronald, 1970-1977; 2 (Box 61)
    - Sullivan, John, 1975-1980 (Box 61)
    - Terrill, Richard, 1989 (Box 61)
    - Turco, Lewis, 1978 (Box 61)
    - Vogelsang, Arthur, 1976-1977 (Box 61)
    - Wakefield, Dan, 1970 (Box 61)
    - Wakoski, Diane, 1974-1978 (Box 61)
    - Weaver, Gordon, 1974-1978 (Box 61)
    - Weiss, Theodore, 1976-1977 (Box 61)
    - Wiebe, Dallas, 1976-1978 (Box 61)
    - Wiggins, Marianne, 1992 (Box 61)
    - Williams, Joy, 1980 (Box 61)
    - Williams, Tom, 1977 (Box 61)
    - Wilson, Robley and Susan Hubbard, 1977-2006 (Box 61)
    - Regarding: Wolfe, Tom, 1990-2006 (Box 61)
    - Youngman, Arline, 1976-1977 (Box 61)
  - New Fiction
    These files consist of interviews and other material stemming from Bellamy's work on the book The New Fiction: Interviews with Innovative American Writers (circa 1974).
    - Ronald Sukenick Interview, circa 1970; 7 (Box 61)
    - Kurt Vonnegut Interview, circa 1968; 2 (Box 61)
    - Tom Wolfe Interview, circa 1970; 5 (Box 61)
    - Interview Book Core - Notes, etc., 2 (Box 62)
    - Innovative Writers - Table of Contents (Box 62)
    - The New Fiction Reviews (Box 62)
    - John Barth Interviews, circa 1972; 6 (Box 62)
    - Donald Barthelme Interview, circa 1970s (Box 62)
    - Robert Boles Interview, circa 1969; 7 (Box 62)
    - Harry Crews Interview, circa 1973 (Box 62)
    - John Gardner Interview, circa 1973 (Box 62)
    - William Gass Interview, circa 1970s (Box 62)
    - John Hawkes Interview, circa 1970s (Box 62)
    - Jerzy Kosinski Interview, circa 1971; 2 (Box 62)
    - Vladimir Nabokov Interview, circa 1970s (Box 63)
    - Ishmael Reed Interview, circa 1972 (Box 63)
    - New Journalism Interview (Box 63)
  - Fiction International
    These files consist of correspondence, grant applications, and other material stemming from Bellamy's work as editor of the literary journal, Fiction International.
    - Editorials (Box 63)
    - Offset Originals (Box 63)
    - Application Forms, 5 (Box 63)
    - Brochures (Box 63)
    - "Faculty Invites, etc." (Box 63)
    - Writers Conference (Box 63)
    - CCLM Executive Director Job (Box 63)
    - F.I. Transition (Box 63)
    - Defense of Magazine, 1979 (Box 63)
    - SLU Fiction Award, 2 (Box 63)
    - CCLM Grant Application, 1981 (Box 63)
    - Printing Estimates, 2 (Box 63)
    - Grant Fiscal Report to CCLM, 1978 (Box 63)
    - Application Guidelines, 1980-1981 (Box 63)
    - 1981 CCLM Grant, 1980-1982 (Box 63)
    - Camera-ready Copy for 1982 Ad (Box 63)
    - Current Magazine Receipts, 1980-1981 (Box 63)
    - NEA Applications, 1978 (Box 63)
    - F.I. Enclosure (Box 63)
    - San Diego State University Press, circa 1983-1986; 3 (Box 63)
    - San Diego State University Press (continued), circa 1983-1986 (Box 64)
    - Grant Fiscal Report, 1980 (Box 64)
    - Miscellaneous Charges (Box 64)
    - CCLM Current Application, 1982 (Box 64)
    - "F.I. 13 - Finances" (Box 64)
    - "F.I. Receipt" (Box 64)
    - CCLM Grant, 1980 (Box 64)
    - The Falcon Correspondence, 1971 (Box 64)
    - Correspondence, 1974-1985 (Box 64)
    - San Diego State University Press - Pre-Millennial Catalogue, 1998 (Box 64)
    - Remarks for National Council on the Arts, 1991 (Box 64)
    - Fiction International Rubber Stamp (St. Lawrence University), undated (Box 59)
  - Writing Files, 1962-2007
    These files consist of drafts and manuscripts for books and associated documentation, and other material broadly relating to Bellamy's various literary endeavors.
    - Associated Writing Programs Correspondence, 1990-1998 (Box 64)
    - NEA - Creative Writing, 1984 (Box 64)
    - NEA - Grant Application (Box 64)
    - NEA - Publishing Panel, Distribution and Special Projects (Box 64)
    - NEA - Appointment Books, 1991-1992 (Box 64)
    - Appointment Books, 1991-1992 (Box 64)
    - Brightleaf Prospectus, 1997 (Box 64)
    - Miscellaneous Invitations, 1970-2001 (Box 64)
    - Christmas Cards, 1991 (Box 64)
    - Miscellaneous Letters, 1967-1998 (Box 64)
    - Interview with Carolyn Forche, 1978 (Box 64)
    - Illinois University Press Correspondence, 1973-1982; 2 (Box 64)
    - Recent Illinois Correspondence, 1985-1996 (Box 65)
    - University of Missouri Press, 1992-1995 (Box 65)
    - Literary Luxeries Cover Art (Box 65)
    - Loose Letters, 1980-1981 (Box 65)
    - Washington Post Book World, 1979-1980 (Box 65)
    - Recommendation Letters, circa 1970-1998 (Box 65)
    - Best American Short Stories, circa 1986 (Box 65)
    - MFA Preparation and Exams, 1968 (Box 65)
    - Professional Contacts, 1974 (Box 65)
    - Future of Literature, 1980 (Box 65)
    - Fiction Panel - Buffalo, 1977 (Box 65)
    - H.S. Writers Conference at Saranac, circa 1990 (Box 65)
    - Superfiction Reviews and Ads, circa 1975 (Box 65)
    - American Fiction Since 1965, circa 1973 (Box 65)
    - Superfiction / Droll and Murderous (Box 65)
    - "Fiction in the Age of Excess" - Saturday Review, 1975 (Box 65)
    - Forways Inward essay, circa 1974 (Box 65)
    - Droll and Murderous - Copies of Permission Forms, circa 1971-1974 (Box 65)
    - Atomic Love, circa 1991-1993
      - Arkansas Magazine and Letter to Publishers Weekly, 1993 (Box 65)
      - Ploughshares Correspondence (with Beautiful Vases manuscript), 1991 (Box 65)
      - Publicity Materials, etc., circa 1992-1993 (Box 65)
      - Atomic Love manuscript, 2 (Box 65)
      - Xeroxes of Publicity, etc., circa 1993; 2 (Box 65)
      - Sunoco (Box 65)
      - Atomic Love manuscript (Box 66)
      - Beautiful Vases (Box 66)
      - Atomic Love manuscript (Box 66)
      - Atomic Love press (Box 66)
      - Atomic Love flyers (Box 66)
      - Empty Envelope (Box 66)
      - Atomic Love page proofs, 2 (Box 66)
      - Atomic Love - "Julie Christie Rescued in Guatemala" (Box 66)
      - Atomic Love - Manuscript, Correspondence and Review (Box 66)
    - Suzi Sinzinnati, 1964-1992
      - Comments (Box 66)
      - Suzi Publicity, 1989-1990; 3 (Box 66)
      - Suzi Ads, 1990 (Box 66)
      - Publishing Magazines, 1991-1992; 4 (Box 66)
      - Publicity Advertisements, 1991-1992 (Box 66)
      - Publicity Advertisements (continued), 1990; 2 (Box 67)
      - Suzi Sinzinnati material, circa 1979; 5 (Box 67)
      - FBS Magazine, 1977 (Box 67)
      - "Kit (Kitty Parks)", circa 1968 (Box 67)
      - Suzi Sinzinnati papers, circa 1978; 2 (Box 67)
      - "Return to Indian Park" and other Suzi writings (Box 67)
      - "Girl" by Luther Askeland (Box 67)
      - Suzi Sinzinnati writings, 15 (Box 67)
        Included are early versions of Suzi Sinzinnati, titled "The Misadventures of Moke Galenaille" and "The Dropout".
      - Suzi Movie - Sidewalk Productions, 1989 (Box 68)
      - North American Review, September 1980 (Box 68)
      - Sally and Kit Letters (Box 68)
      - Part II, circa 1964 (Box 68)
      - Synopsis (Box 68)
      - Miscellaneous Loose Notes and Manuscript, 4 (Box 68)
      - Misfortunes of Moke Galenaille - The Dropout (Box 68)
      - Miscellaneous Loose Notes and Manuscript, 6 (Box 68)
    - Publishing House Envelopes (Box 68)
    - 12th Annual Old Dominion University, 1989 (Box 68)
    - The American Writers Congress Program, 1981 (Box 68)
    - Unpublished Novel, circa 2007
      - Green Revolution, 3 (Box 68)
      - Green Revolution (continued) (Box 69)
      - Midnight Choir, 3 (Box 69)
    - Vonnegut Statement reviews, circa 1971 (Box 69)
    - The Human Zoo: Justifable Speculations (Box 69)
    - "J.B. Review" photocopy, 1966 (Box 69)
    - Freud's Relation to Romanticism (Box 69)
    - Steamboating, circa 1974 (Box 69)
    - Breadloaf Article, circa 1973 (Box 69)
    - AWP Article, 1979 (Box 69)
    - Iowa Writers Workshop, circa 1987-1994; 5 (Box 69)
    - The Bellamys of Early Virgina, circa 2005
      Included are early versions of Bellamy's book, The Bellamys of Early Virginia (2005), which outlines the Bellamy/Bellomy families.
      - Bound and Unbound drafts, 4 (Box 69)
      - Kindred Spirits drafts, 2 (Box 70)
    - Harper's Magazine, 1962 (Box 70)
    - NEA biography, circa 1990-1991 (Box 70)
    - Olympic Gold Medalist, circa 1978; 2 (Box 70)
    - Loose Flyers, 2007 (Box 70)
    - "The New World" Extra draft, circa 2005 (Box 70)
    - The Lost Saranac Interviews, 2006-2007
      - "Printers Proof photos to Joe and Connie", circa 2007 (Box 70)
      - Attraction photos and brochures, circa 1974- 2006 (Box 70)
        Computer disks are restricted. Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services:
        2007.ycal.11018.0001: Photo Slide show from Fiction International / St. Lawrence University
      - Interviews, Permissions and Recollections, circa 2006 (Box 70)
      - Interviews draft, circa 2006; 2 (Box 70)
      - Photo Proofs from Lost Saranac Interviews, circa 2006; 2 (Box 70)
    - Biography and News Release, 1991 (Box 70)
    - Roth's Deadman, circa 1992 (Box 70)
    - Weeds of Ohio (Box 70)
    - Iowa's Writers Workshop Newsletter, 1990-1991 (Box 70)
    - Midwestern Book Review (Hungry Mind), 1993 (Box 70)
    - Canaras Writing Weekend, Sept. 7-8, 1990 (Box 70)
    - Writers Series (Intro), circa 2000 (Box 70)
    - Ballantine Correspondence, 2007 (Box 70)
    - Old Related Stories (Box 70)
    - Northampton, circa 1973 (Box 70)
    - Report on Stamford Creative Writing Program, 1980 (Box 70)
  - Writings By Others, 1971-2001
    - "Blasters: American Short Stories" manuscript, edited by Robert Shapard and James Thomas, 1985 (Box 71)
    - "Larabi's Ox: Stories of Morocco" manuscript, by Tony Ardizzone, 1992 (Box 71)
    - "Burning Marguerite" manuscript, by Elizabeth Inness-Brown, 2001; 3 (Box 71)
    - "Broken Angels" manuscript, by Debi Elramey, 1999; 2 (Box 71)
    - "The Vonnegut Conspiracy" manuscript, by Jerry Klinkowitz, 1971 (Box 71)
    - "Iowa Writers; Workship" manuscript, by Steve Wilbers, 1982 (Box 71)
    - "Living Alone" manuscript, by Rob Wilson, 1978 (Box 71)
    - "Travelers" manuscript (early version of Here ), by Elizabeth Inness-Brown, circa 1994 (Box 71)
    - "The Explosion-of-the-Month Club" manuscript, by Steve Amick, 1986 (Box 71)
    - "Literary Disruptions" manuscript, by Jerry Klinkowitz, 1990 (Box 71)
    - "Home Fires" manuscript, by David Long, 1983 (Box 71)
    - "Handiwork" manuscript, by Jim Clark, 1998 (Box 72)